<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!-- Created by XML:Wrench -->
<root>
  <!-- content of XML goes 'here'  -->
  <mobBosses>
           <mobBoss>
                   <name>Giovanni Morietti</name>
                   <lossCondition>Giovanni is trying to worm his way into the woodwork of the city, taking over businesses and even politicians to gain a seat of power. Once Giovanni succeeds in corrupting 5 targets he wins.</lossCondition>
                   <ongoingEffect>Giovanni has placed 5 of his lieutenants throughout the city to try and take control of it. Every turn the lieutenants make progress in corrupting their target. The players will need to investigate an area in order to find a lieutenant which will initiate a special situation card to resolve it. If one lieutenant is resolved, another takes his place. Once the players resolve 5 lieutenants, Giovanni will be revealed as another situation card and will need to be resolved as well in order for the players to win. </ongoingEffect>
                   <modifier>Police corruption from situatiuon cards gain get a 1.5 times modifier.</modifier>
                   <story>
                     The Morietti's have been a strong family, always have since way back in the times of the motherland, and that hasn't changed here in this brave new world. The family's name demands respect, power, and fear. As much as others would wish to delude themselves that they hold all the power, you know the truth. That power is within the blood. The spilling of it, and the relations it provides. Family is a tool, Giovanni's most powerful one, driven by the blood he and his own all share, it connects and unites, and gives him purpose. \nGiovanni's been groomed since birth to take up the mantle of the don, to succeed his father and lead his family to even further glory. He's learned much from those around him, how to push the right buttons, where to hide his dealings, and when the use of force is required. But one thing Giovanni's learned from watching his father is the complacency of the powerful. It boggled his mind how despite all of his old man's wisdom, he seemed blind to how his lack of a drive to move forward was making the family suffer. There was no more growth, in place of that was a slow dwindling of power and resources. \nBut that's all going to change now, that the old man has stepped down in his old age, letting the new generation take the reigns. Giovannis is now the don, and he knows it's his time now. And he won't roll over and yield to those who think they own this city, no. Blood is power, and Giovanni plans to get more of it, whether through fresh new bodies willing to serve, or spilling it from his enemies and letting it course through the veins of his city. As long as it's all flowing to him.
                   </story>
           </mobBoss>
           <mobBoss>
                   <name>Jon Biers</name>
                   <lossCondition>Jon's goal is to initiate anarchy throughout the city, he has a list of targets that he wishes to take out in order to do so. If he succeeds with 5 of them, he wins.</lossCondition>
                   <ongoingEffect>
                     Once every 3 turns Jon Biers will attack a random target and initiate a special situation that the players have a chance of resolving. If the players succeed 5 times, they win, if Jon succeeds 5 times he wins.
                   </ongoingEffect>
                   <modifier>Chaos increases from situation cards have a 1.5 times multiplier.</modifier>
                   <story>
                     People are a hoot. No, really, they are. Jon Biers loves people, they make the most insane decisions, never ceasing to amuse. Jon found early on in life that most hobbies and pastimes just couldn't keep his attention, he'd gotten so used to the boredom, that he grew numb to the constant chewing he felt on his insides. This boredom, Jon knew would kill him. But that all changed with the accident. A factory blowing up one day jolted Jon from his fugue and roused him to watch on in curiosity. The sight Jon saw made him immediately fall in love. \nThe people, all of them around him, the screaming, the sobbing, the wailing, and the watching, all of it made Jon's heart race like never before. He watched as the workers first hobbled out, followed by the stragglers dragging their bodies away from the raging inferno. Limbs were torn, tatters of men were strewn about, some of this refuse Jon realized were the workers still trying to escape, more corpses than men now. He couldn't look away, away from these people who were living and dying so fantastically in a singular explosive moment. Except when Jon realized he wasn't alone. There was a crowd of people beside him, around him, watching as he was. None of them so much as budged to help the workers, some were gasping, others looked away, more than half seemed content to just stare passively. And Jon found himself falling even deeper in love. \nHe couldn't help it, these reactions, these emotions, how the whole area was charged with an energy, Jon was enthralled by it all. And so, he took to watching people, and for a time, he was satisfied. But soon, monotony set in. Jon realized that people had one key flaw, they cling to security, stability, and the tedium of everyday life. And that's just so boring. He couldn't go back to how things were, not after that first thrill, he needed to light that spark again. Jon began to kidnap others, forcing them into situations for his amusement, and tossing them aside as he broke them. \nAs Biers continued his work, he slowly began to realize that he was growing bored…. Again! These isolated experiences helped, but it just wasn't the same as the first time. Jon needed more, he needed to make it bigger. And that's when he began planning. Jon needed to assemble help of course, gather others who would be more than willing to assist him in his endeavour. Luckily, Jon's constant observation of people had leant him the ability to charm others quite thoroughly, some would say he had a silver tongue, but all it really was, was telling people what they wanted to hear, nothing too difficult about that. Where words couldn't suffice, money did. As Jon gained footholds and power his name itself could convince others to join him. \nBut now, now he was reaching critical mass. Jon decided that it was about time to enact the grand finale. To engulf the whole city in that first moment, to destroy the pillars that hold this city stagnant, and let anarchy reign. And maybe then he would finally be satisfied. Or maybe not. Only one way to find out, really.
                   </story>
           </mobBoss>
           <mobBoss>
                   <name>Beau Wilkins</name>
                   <lossCondition>Beau is attempting to build an empire on bootleg moonshine. He has 4 distilleries hidden throughout the city, over time they will generate revenue for him, once he has reached a certain amount he wins. Losing a distillery mean less cash flow of course, the players have the chance to search a district and find a distillery. Once one is found it acts like a situation card that needs to be resolved.</lossCondition>
                   <ongoingEffect>Every turn Beau will get a certain amount of revenue based on how much distilleries are running. Every 6 turns Beau will increase either police corruption, chaos, or mafia presence by 5.</ongoingEffect>
                   <modifier>N/A</modifier>
                   <story>
                     Beau knows his manners, he was raised respectfully of course. His Ma made sure of that. Everyday since he was thirteen he'd wake at the crack of dawn and help maintain the land with his kin. From sunrise to sunset he would work ‘till his bones creaked, but it was all for the good of the family, for his Pa, his Ma, his brothers, sisters, cousins, and more. Things were going well until the farm dried up. \nThe land grew harsher and harsher over the years, refusing to give back what they put into it. Pa wilted along with the land, until he died no longer able to take the shame of it all. It fell on Beau to provide for the family from then on. Unlike Pa, Beau grew tougher from the land, harsher on the exterior as well as the interior. He knew he'd need to find some other form of income for his family, and Beau knew exactly how he'd do that. \nSee, Beau knew the city-slickers thought they were above it all, different from him and his kin, what with their highfalutin ways. But it was all an act, in the end they had they same wants and desires as Beau, and Beau knew that booze, was most definitely desirable. It was always a real head-scratcher to Beau as to why the fancy folk thought they could just get rid of booze. But Beau could see an opportunity when one was presented to him, he understood when there was less corn people wanted more of it, with less tomatoes people wanted more, with less booze to go around he knew people would want more. \nIt was a good thing that Beau and some of his buddies knew their way around a distillery. So, seeing an easy way to provide for his family, Beau, some of his kin, and his closest friends set off for Bower City, ready to establish a market. Beau knew it would be more… unsavory work in the eyes of the law. But hell, Pa always taught that any work worth doin' was the hard and dirty kind.
                   </story>
           </mobBoss>
           <mobBoss>
                   <name>Ricky Veers</name>
                   <lossCondition>Ricky and his gang are trying to rob the biggest bank in Bower City, once the progress bar of the heist has been filled, it's game over.</lossCondition>
                   <ongoingEffect>Every turn depending on the status of overall chaos and mafia presence progress will be made on the bank heist.</ongoingEffect>
                   <modifier>N/A</modifier>
                   <story>
                     Ricky grew up on the streets as the runt of the litter of a family of seven. Ever since he could remember he had to bite and scrape to get at not what he wanted, but what he needed. Everyday was a constant struggle for young Ricky, fighting for scraps and bits of food that could tide himself over as his brothers did the same while his parents fought drunkenly in the background. \nAs Ricky grew though, he left the confines of his shoddy apartment, spending less and less time living with his family and making a life out out on the streets. Whatever it took to survive, he'd do, pickpocketing mostly, but this over time changed to stealing, then breaking and entering, it eventually got to a point where Ricky would actively shake others down with more… physical measures. \nAs Ricky's success grew his fellow scum and unwanted began to take note, emulating his actions with varying success. Veers knew that he could spin this to his advantage and began to round up his peers, teaching them how to properly steal and intimidate the right people, slowly increasing his power base and becoming the de facto leader of this band of riff-raff. \nAs his group grew, Ricky began to branch out with recruiting to his group. Hiring the right kinds of muscle, the more notorious types of talent, all the while ramping up his game, taking on bigger and bigger jobs. But Ricky's eyes were always on the end goal, the last big heist he'd need to make to live the easy life. \nJust that last heist, and then he'd be set for life.
                   </story>
           </mobBoss>
           <mobBoss>
                   <name>Sergei Rostislav</name>
                   <lossCondition>Sergei is attempting to recruit members into his family, he has placed three secret recruiting centers throughout the city. The recruitment centers will churn out a certain amount of new recruits every turn depending on the district's mafia presence value and chaos value. Once Sergei has reached a certain number of recruits he will be too powerful for the police to withstand and win.</lossCondition>
                   <ongoingEffect>
                     Every turn the recruitment centers will produce a number of new recruits based on the district's police corruption value and chaos value that it is located in. Players will be able to investigate a district for a recruitment center, once one is found it will be represented by a situation card, depending on the number of recruits the the center has made, the difficulty will be adjusted. Once all 3 centers have been dealt with Sergei will be revealed as a situation card himself, that must be dealt with before he escapes.
                   </ongoingEffect>
                   <modifier>1.5 times modifier to mafia presence gain from situation cards.</modifier>
                   <story>
                     Sergei was raised knowing the world's a cruel place. From the very beginning his parents groomed him to be the perfect boss for the Rostislav family, by making sure he was present for every sordid act they would commit. Someone stealing from the funds? Cut off one of his hands. A family member ratted them out? Crush his limbs and gouge out his tongue. A fed was getting too close for comfort? Capture his five year old daughter and send her back piece by piece. Evisceration was a big part of Sergei's childhood. \nSergei grew up learning that in order to be on top of it all, to conquer this world that wanted nothing but to devour you, you needed to be crueller than it. To be able to bite back harder and to instill as much fear in your enemies as you could. His parents made sure of that. There was one thing that they never could understand though. \nWhen Sergei's mother was captured by another family, his father flew into rage. The family swept through streets and communities destroying everything and killing everyone. His father was able to save his mother, with great cost to the family, hundreds of their numbers now dead. So Sergei dealt with his parents, and took over as the head. He would show this world cruelty, but he'd do it with a cold heart, frozen and impenetrable. \nOf course he would need time to reestablish the family, to let their strength grow back to what it once was, and he knew just where to start.
                   </story>
           </mobBoss>
    
  </mobBosses>
</root>