<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!-- Created by XML:Wrench -->
<root>
  <!-- content of XML goes 'here'  -->
  <tutorialpages>
    <page>"Welcome to Bower City. I'm Police Chief Bob Walsh. Bower City is a metropolis with 5 main districts; Downtown, Portside, The Boxes, Suburbia, and Stony Gate. Bower City is the most peaceful town anyone could ask for."</page>
    
    <page>"At least, that's what I wish I could tell you."</page>
    
    <page>"Unfortunately, I can't. We, at the Bower City Police Department have our work cut out for us. Crime is at an all-time high. We have crimes ranging from bank heists to car chases to alcohol and cargo smuggling."</page>
    
    <page>"We know that the mafia controls most of the crime here, some of the other crimes are just low-lifes being low-lifes. We don't really know who's the head honcho though, the main guy pulling all the strings, or even why he's doing it."</page>

    <page>"This is where you come in. We need you and your team of fellow coppers to pound the streets. This means selecting the crimes you wish get involved in, learning about the cases, and getting the job done."</page>

    <page>"Now, getting the job done may be different than what you are used to, or even what you've seen. Here at Bower City, everything is turned based; hey, I didn't make up these rules. Anyway, during your turn you have several different choices: Lower Crime, Change Neighborhood, Draw Situation, Resolve Situation, and Player Special Action."</page>

    <page>"Lowering Crime costs a stat or resource you may or may not have. Changing Neighborhoods is what it seems to be; you change what neighborhood you are in, it can really matter. Drawing a situation card means finding a new crime to pursue, good things and bad things could happen from this. Resolve a situation; this one is a little like Lowering crime; it costs stats that you may or may not have in your possession. Player Special Action; this is a favorite of some of the other coppers down at the station; each person has a special that can be used to help with various scenarios. Player Special Actions are different for everyone here, make sure you know what your special is."</page>

    <page>"Be warned, using a Player Special Action could be the difference of life and death; that door swings both ways by the way. Oh, I almost forgot, Situations and Lowering crime will most likely cost more stats than one officer possesses and may take more than one turn to do so, your fellow officers here with you could help out."</page>
    
    <page>“With a little luck we -meaning you- might find clues as to who the big mastermind of this whole crime syndicate is.”</page>

    <page>"I will check up on you later. Good luck out there."</page>
  </tutorialpages>
</root>